You can't bury the past.
Old Henry is a western, action, drama film directed by Potsy Ponciroli.
A widowed farmer and his son warily take in a
mysterious, injured man with a satchel of cash.
When a posse of men claiming to be the law come for the
money, the farmer must decide who to trust.
Defending a siege of his homestead, the farmer reveals a talent for gun-slinging
that surprises everyone calling his true identity into question.
Henry, played by Tim Blake Nelson.
Curry, played by Scott Haze.
Wyatt, played by Gavin Lewis.
Ketchum, played by Stephen Dorff.
Al, played by Trace Adkins.
Dugan, played by Richard Speight Jr..
Old Henry is a 2021 American western action drama film
written and directed by Potsy Ponciroli.
It stars Tim Blake Nelson as the titular character, a farmer who must protect his son from outlaws,
with Scott Haze, Gavin Lewis, Trace Adkins, and Stephen Dorff in supporting roles.
The film had its world premiere at the Venice Film Festival on September 7,
2021, and was theatrically released in the United States by Shout!
Studios on October 1.
It was critically acclaimed for the story, Ponciroli's
direction, and Nelson's performance.
The National Board of Review selected the film in its annual
list of the Top Ten Independent Films of the year.
The film explores themes of double cross, hidden cache,
headstrong son, hell unleashed, old west legend.
The tone is emotional.